Contact

mubienaime@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bien-aime-mugabarigira-9692126b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Programming

HTML

Information Technology

Languages

French (Professional Working)
English (Professional Working)
Kinyarwanda (Native or Bilingual)

Publications

Context-Aware Navigator for Road Safety in Vehicular Cyber-Physical Systems

Context-Aware Navigation Protocol for Safe Driving in Vehicular Cyber-Physical Systems

Context-Aware Navigator Protocol for IP-Based Vehicular Networks

Vehicular Mobility Management for IP-Based Vehicular Networks

IPv6 Vehicular Communications over IEEE 802.11-OCB Wireless Link

Bien Aime MUGABARIGIRA

A PhD Candidate with a research interests including intelligent transportation systems, wireless networks, and Vehicular Ad-hoc Networks (VANET).

Gyeonggi, South Korea

Summary

I am an Ph.D Candidate in the College of Information & Communication Engineering of Sungkyunkwan University since 2015. My MS and Ph.D advisor is Professor Jaehoon (Paul) Jeong. I got a BS degree in 2012 from former National University of Rwanda (NUR) Current University of Rwanda (UR). My major was the Faculty of Applied Sciences, Department of Computer Sciences.

My life motto is "to bless and embrace by making every effort to live at peace with others, sharing and gathering in love". I live to inspire hope to people.

Experience

Sungkyunkwan University 8 years 10 months

Researcher PHD Student August 2015 - Present (8 years 10 months) Suwon, Republic of Korea

Teaching Assistant
March 2021 - June 2021 (4 months)

Suwon, Republic of Korea

Course: Infrastructure Networks and Security

Teaching Assistant

March 2020 - December 2020 (10 months)

Suwon, Republic of Korea

Course: Introduction to Computer Networks

Teaching Assistant

September 2015 - December 2015 (4 months)

South Korea

Course: Creative Design Project

Education

University of Rwanda

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (January 2009 - November 2012)

Sungkyunkwan University
PhD Candidate, Computer Engineering